ensembleiq.com 2017-06-28

# Privacy | EnsembleIQ

French Text Follows the English

Eagle Operating Corp. d/b/a EnsembleIQ and its subsidiaries (collectively referred to as “Company” or “we”) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This privacy policy applies to the following websites, as well as the website you are currently accessing (if not on the following list):

• EnsembleIQ: [http://www.EnsembleIQ.com/home](http://www.ensembleiq.com/home)  
• Apparel Magazine: <http://apparel.edgl.com/home>  
• The Canadian Coffee & Tea Show: <http://coffeeteashow.ca/>  
• Canadian Grocer: <http://www.canadiangrocer.com/>  
• Canadian Healthcare Network: <http://www.canadianhealthcarenetwork.ca/> and <http://www.professionsante.ca/>  
• Carbonview Research: <http://www.carbonview.com/>  
• CCentral: <http://ccentral.ca/>  
• Consumer Goods Technology: <http://www.consumergoods.com/>  
• The Convenience U Carwacs Show: <http://calgary.convenienceu.ca/>  
• Convenience Store News: <http://www.csnews.com/>  
• Convenience Store News for Single Store Owners: <http://www.csnews.com/single-store-owner>  
• EKN Research: <http://eknresearch.com/>  
• FoodBiz: <http://foodbiz.ca/>  
• The Gourmet Retailer: <http://www.gourmetretailer.com/>  
• Hospitality Technology: <http://hospitalitytechnology.edgl.com/home>  
• Le Salon des Dépanneurs: <http://salondec.com/>  
• Monday Report on Retailers: <http://www.mondayreport.ca/>  
• Path to Purchase Institute: <https://p2pi.org/>  
• Path to Purchase Expo: <http://www.path2purchaseexpo.com/>  
• Shopper Marketing: <http://www.shoppermarketingmag.com/home/>  
• Pharmacy U: <http://pharmacyu.ca/>  
• Progressive Grocer: <http://www.progressivegrocer.com/>  
• RIS News: <http://www.risnews.com/>  
• Retail Leader: <http://www.retailleader.com/>  
• Retail Buyers: <http://retailbuyers.net/>  
• Shopper Marketing Summit: <http://www.shoppersummit.com/>  
• Store Brands: <http://www.storebrands.info/>  
• StratConn: <http://www.stratconn.org/>  
• Top Women in Grocery: <http://www.topwomeningrocery.progressivegrocer.com/>

Amendments to this privacy policy will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of any of our websites following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof. By visiting the present website or any of the foregoing websites, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE GATHER?**

• We receive and store any information you enter on our websites or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features.  
• We may also receive information about you from other sources and add it to your account information. This information might be public information or data you provided with necessary and proper permissions.  
• We use the information that we gather for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future visits for you, improving our online store, notifying you of new products and services, conducting market research, and otherwise communicating with you.  
• We participate in multiple ad networks. When you visit our websites, these networks place a cookie on your browser. These cookies contain no Personally Identifiable Information (PII). They identify you as a visitor to our website, and allow us or our clients to display relevant advertising to you both on our site, and after you leave our site on ad placements throughout the ad networks’ participating websites. To opt out of the targeted advertising provided by EnsembleIQ, please visit the National Advertising Initiative opt-out page: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.  
• We gather date, time, certain information about a user's browser and system or device configuration and capabilities, navigation history and IP address for all visitors to our websites.  
We use this information for our internal audit log, for trend analysis and system administration, and to gather broad information about our audiences and their geographic locations. Non-personal demographic and profile data is used to tailor your experience at our websites, showing you content we think might be of interested to you. This information may also be shared with advertisers on an aggregate and/or non-personal basis.  
• Visitors to EnsembleIQ websites should understand that by using these websites, information may be collected about them via cookies placed on their hard drive to enhance or customize the experience. By visiting any of our websites, you give us permission for the use of cookies for this purpose.  
• Other third party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users’ activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness, to deliver targeted advertising, or for other reasons. We are not responsible for the use of information obtained or shown to visitors as a result of the data collected by third party advertisers.  
• We use cookies and common data collection technologies, including associated web beacons and transparent GIFs associated with cookies, on our newsletters and in our email campaigns to collect information both on an aggregate and individual basis.

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU**

• We share customer information with trusted agents and partners who work to perform functions on our behalf, including data processing, order and publication fulfillment, sending postal mail and e-mail, processing credit card payments, providing customer service, and providing marketing assistance (including direct and targeted marketing).  
• We may send offers on behalf of our carefully selected business partners, or you may receive offers directly from our business partners. Our business partners include all of our affiliated companies as well as oth
